<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ORAI China</title><link>http://localhost:1313/en/</link><description>Recent content on ORAI China</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>运筹OR帷幄</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[TechTalk No. 41] Columbia DRO Tianyi Peng: When A/B Testing Platforms Meet Reinforcement Learning</title><link>http://localhost:1313/en/techtalk/techtalk_41/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/en/techtalk/techtalk_41/</guid><description>A novel &amp;ldquo;Difference-in-Q&amp;rdquo; (DQ) estimator, based on reinforcement learning, is proposed to address the Interference problem in A/B testing. DQ outperforms traditional estimators in bias-variance trade-off, reducing bias and exponentially decreasing variance. Collaborating with ByteDance, DQ achieved a 99% reduction in mean squared error in large-scale commercial scenarios.</description></item><item><title>[OR Talk No. 22] CityU Lishuai Li &amp; Xinyu He: A Route Network Planning Method for Urban Air Delivery</title><link>http://localhost:1313/en/ortalk/ortalk_22/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/en/ortalk/ortalk_22/</guid><description>High-tech companies are investing in drone technologies for urban air delivery to address last-mile delivery issues and reduce road traffic congestion. Effective traffic management is crucial for scaling up these services in dense urban environments. This paper introduces a tube-based ConOps route network planning method, which decouples the NP-hard network planning problem into single-path problems and uses a space cost function for dense route design. Tests show this method generates near-optimal routes with significant computational time savings.</description></item><item><title>[InTalk S5E3] Lenovo: Practical Application of Operations Research in Material Requirement Planning within Lenovo's Supply Chain</title><link>http://localhost:1313/en/intalk/intalk_s5e3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/en/intalk/intalk_s5e3/</guid><description>This lecture will introduce Material Requirement Planning (MRP), explaining its fundamental concepts and significance. It will then discuss common MRP solutions and analyze the main challenges encountered during implementation. Finally, the lecture will present Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s MRP system based on intelligent decision-making technology, highlighting its unique advantages in improving efficiency and optimizing resource management.</description></item><item><title>InTalk: Industry Analysis &amp; Future Trends</title><link>http://localhost:1313/en/landing/intalks_intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/en/landing/intalks_intro/</guid><description>Over the past five quarters, Industry Talk has focused on operations research application scenarios such as intelligent decision-making, energy, and finance. We have invited heavyweight guests from startups to industry leaders to present the latest developments in these sectors. These discussions not only analyzed the core challenges faced by various industries but also showcased the crucial role and development trends of operations research in these fields.
In the future, we will continue to explore more industry themes and encourage everyone to put forward valuable opinions and suggestions to jointly promote the development and progress of the industry.</description></item><item><title>ORTalk: Sparking Academic Inspirations</title><link>http://localhost:1313/en/landing/ortalks_intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/en/landing/ortalks_intro/</guid><description>OR Talk is dedicated to providing in-depth interpretations and wide-ranging promotion of academic achievements. We invite expert guests to share their latest scholarly accomplishments or to conduct thorough analyses and discussions of classic and trending topics. Through these fascinating presentations and open discussions, OR Talk aims to unveil the trends in technological development, analyze the core challenges faced, and bring about a profound brainstorming experience for all participants.
Moreover, through community interactions and exchanges, participants can not only meet like-minded friends but also collectively &amp;ldquo;level up&amp;rdquo; on their academic exploration journey.</description></item><item><title>TechTalk: Technical Insights into the Future</title><link>http://localhost:1313/en/landing/techtalks_intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/en/landing/techtalks_intro/</guid><description>Tech Talk focuses on the application of academic achievements in real-world scenarios. In each issue, we invite industry experts to share their experiences and insights on successfully applying technological theories to practical problems. Through sharing and Q&amp;amp;A sessions, the entire process from &amp;ldquo;problem discovery - research exploration - practical application&amp;rdquo; is presented, guiding participants to gain an in-depth understanding of the stories behind technological practices and providing guidance for technological exploration in specific domains.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to ORAI China</title><link>http://localhost:1313/en/landing/landing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/en/landing/landing/</guid><description>Bridge the chasm between academia and industry &amp;amp; span the gulf between theory and practice.</description></item></channel></rss>